Gilbert Eduardo Chávez Guillen

Angular developer | Full Stack developer

Valencia, Venezuela (time zone GMT-4) (+58) 424 4606538 gilbertcg99@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/gilbert-chavez-guillen gilbertchavezdev.com

Web developer with **+4 years** of experience in web and mobile development (Angular, Ionic). I also handle certain backend technologies like nodejs, express.js to handle side projects in my free time. This has proven my capacity to learn new technologies and ways to develop software. My passion is frontend development, but no matter the technology or project, I guarantee you that my positive attitude and adaptability will always be present.

EXPERIENCE

Kenility, Angular developer — March 2022 - Present

- I reduced the development time of the frontend team by 10% by implementing a dynamic configuration by environment for the use of the languages of an Angular project.
- Implement dynamic table components to increase development speed by 50% in an Angular project.
- I reduced the loading time of a messaging project with Ngrx applying Lazy loading and integrated different APIs for the communication of different apps through it.

Tech Stack: Angular, Firebase, NgRx, Scrum, Ingles, Github.

Cromatik Media — September 2020 - Present

- I developed an application from the beginning to its distribution in the AppStore and PlayStore that geolocates supermarkets in the city of Valencia Venezuela and generates comparative lists.
- I led the development of different informative web portals for a team of three people.

Tech Stack: Angular, Ionic, Nodejs, Express.js, MongoDB, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Wordpress.

Protos Tech — September 2019 - February 2022

- I improved the performance of a CRM by 50% in loading speed for the user and in compilation speed by updating angular to the most current version and removing the use of nebular for the project that no longer needed it.
- Led the frontend team of a CRM project from start to production for 1 year and a half.

Tech Stack: Angular, Nodejs, Express.js, MongoDB, Mysql, Nebular, Strapi, Socket.io, Gitlab, Scrum.

Witty Growth — April 2019 - september 2019

- I implemented automated tests that managed to give stability to the main product of the company.
- I developed a multi-currency system for the financial application, with the expectation of expanding the application by 20% of new users

Tech Stack: Symphony, PHP, HTML, CSS. JavaScript, Selenium

Colorados Venezuela — June 2018 - November 2018

- I completed my internship stage at the University of Carabobo.
- I developed a system of dynamic forms that streamlined the administrative operations of the company by 60%.

Tech Stack: Angular, HTML, CSS, Javascript.

PROJECTS

Move Vzla (Cromatik Media) - move.cromaikmedia.com - Dec. 2020 - Present

Mobile app for geolocation of supermarkets in the city of Valencia, Venezuela. Rol: Fullstack developer, Tech leader.

Prospect growth system (Protos Tech) - pgs-consulting.com/crm - Jul. 2020 - feb. 2022

Platform for managing the client portfolio of the insurance agency PGS Consulting. Rol: Fullstack developer, frontend leader.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Advanced: JavaScript, TypeScrip, HTML. CSSt; Basic: PHP, C.

Frameworks and Tools: Advanced: Angular, Ionic; Intermediate: Node.js, Express.js, Electron.js;

Data Base: Advanced: MongoDB; Intermediate: Mysql;

Agile: Scrum, Kanban

Languages: Basic: English; Native: Spanish.

EDUCATION

University of Carabobo - Valencia, Carabobo.

Bachelor's degree in computer science. 2011 - Present. (10th semester)

CERTIFICATIONS

REDUX en Angular con NGRX: Desde las bases hasta la práctica - Udemy. jun. 2022.

Curso práctico de maquetación css - Platzi. Apr. 2022.

Curso de fundamentos de angular - Platzi. Apr. 2022.

Curso definitivo de html y css - Platzi. March. 2022.

Curso principios SOLID y clean code - Udemy. Feb. 2023.

<u>Curso basico de mongo</u> – Platzi. Dec. 2022.

Curso de comunicación con slack - Platzi. Dec. 2022.

Curso de TypeScript: Programación Orientada a Objetos y Asincronismo! - Platzi. Nov. 2022.

Curso de TypeScript: Tipos Avanzados y Funciones! - Platzi. Nov. 2022

Curso Básico de Jenkins - Platzi. Jul. 2022

Curso de Electron: Apps de escritorio en Windows y Mac - Platzi. Jun. 2022